{
    "subject": "resource/Martinetes",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Andalusian_music",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Martinetes is Andalusian music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9169105887413025,
            "question": "Is Martinetes a popular musical form within Andalusia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7594665884971619,
            "question": "What is the connection between Martinetes and Andalusia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7380005121231079,
            "question": "What kind of music is Martinetes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6165446639060974,
            "question": "What instruments are typically used in Andalusian music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6122933030128479,
            "question": "Are there other musical traditions associated with Andalusia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5726740956306458,
            "question": "Where does Andalusian music originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5497749447822571,
            "question": "How would you describe the typical sound of Andalusian music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5421397686004639,
            "question": "Give an example of a musical genre from Andalusia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5193677544593811,
            "question": "What cultural events often feature Andalusian music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44682905077934265,
            "question": "Can you name any famous Andalusian musicians?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Martinetes is Andalusian music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7622_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What cultural events often feature Andalusian music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7622_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a musical genre from Andalusia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7622_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the typical sound of Andalusian music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7622_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7622_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the martinete, which is described as a type of flamenco dance and song. Flamenco is closely associated with Andalusia in Spain, so it can be concluded that the subject of martinetes involves Andalusian music."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}